<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts on Eric S. Moore</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts on Eric S. Moore</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On This Website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thoughts/on-this-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thoughts/on-this-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let this be the place to learn about the things I love.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Be it writings on my various interests, thoughts on books and philosophy, or a penmanship portfolio, I plan to collect the most worthwhile of my ramblings and give to them a life and a home on this website. I don&amp;rsquo;t honestly expect that anyone will visit my creation, at least for a while, but it makes no difference either way. The website is secondary to my penmanship, reading, writing, and studying. It&amp;rsquo;s only a new element and extension of what I have been doing and will continue to do. It&amp;rsquo;s a place to gather, share, and publish my work; a looming force compelling myself to spend more time developing my passions; and a chance to hone an essential skill of communication: a skill that, like any other, requires endless practice. I want to bring everything together, in one place, where presentation and quality matters.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Apples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thoughts/apples/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thoughts/apples/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sunchaser:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;6/10&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;I wish I could know more about this apple. Apparently, it&amp;rsquo;s a new Walmart&#xA;exclusive. I know no more. That much is a mystery. Greater still is how&#xA;they managed to alchemize an entire watermelon directly into the shell&#xA;of an apple. It has the exact same texture as one near the rind. It even&#xA;tastes like melon, but with a weird anise aftertaste and even a little&#xA;caramel. Light, watery, crunchy, and just barely sweet. Like a bland,&#xA;unripe watermelon.&#xA;(2026.01.03)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Autumn Glory:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;5.25/10&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Results</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/thoughts/apple-rankings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/thoughts/apple-rankings/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
